Jack, we've authenticated the thumb-drive data.
杰克 我们已经鉴定了微型存储器上的数据
Omicron definitely made the Sentox for the military.
欧米克隆公司确实为军方制造了Sentox毒气
- Who is this Henderson? - Someone I used to work for.
- 亨德森是谁?  - 以前我为他工作过
- Where? - CTU.
- 哪?  - CTU
He's the man who recruited me. Things ended badly between us.
是他把我招进来的  后来我们闹僵了
What are accusing me now of, Jack, being in bed with terrorists?
你要指控我什么 杰克 勾结恐怖分子?
I need complete access to Omicron's Sentox program.
我要欧米克隆公司Sentox项目的全部资料
I've got to merge some files,
我必须要合并一些文件
find out who was working on this project.
才能找出谁负责这个项目
We need I.T. They're next door.
我去找IT人员 他们就在隔壁
I listened to everything Bauer had to say about the thumb-drives.
我已经听说了鲍尔了解到的 微储器的信息
CTU does not have enough information to hurt us.
CTU 并没有对我们不利的足够证据
What about Bauer?
那鲍尔呢?
Well, in about one minute, he'll be dead.
还有1分钟可以活
Oh, my God...
天哪...
How could I be so stupid?
我他妈怎么这么蠢
Mr. McGill, we think there might be an attack on President Suvarov's motorcade.
麦克基尔先生 我们认为有人会袭击 苏沃洛夫总统的车队
My people are not going to chase that white elephant.
我的人不会去管这种毫无根据的事情
They're busy trying to locate 19 canisters of Sentox nerve gas.
他们正忙于寻找剩余的19罐神经毒气
Now let my people focus on their work,
请让我的人安心工作
or I will have you escorted out of here!
不然我就找人把你送出去!
Lynn is mentally incapable of running CTU.
林精神有些问题 已经无法管理CTU了
- What are you suggesting? - Section 112.
- 你认为应该怎样做?  - 112号条例
Curtis, take Mr. Stiles and Ms. O'Brian, put them in holding,
柯蒂斯 拿下斯特尔斯先生和奥布赖恩小姐 把他们关起来
and then escort Audrey Raines out of CTU.
然后把奥黛丽・瑞恩斯送出CTU
Lynn McGill, I'm relieving you of your command
林・麦克基尔 我现在解除你的职务
under the "incapacity clause" of section 112.
根据第112号不合格条款
Mrs. Logan is riding with the Suvarovs.
洛根夫人在苏沃洛夫的车上
Get my wife on the phone.
让我妻子接电话
The terrorists were very specific:
恐怖分子说的非常明确
if I don't allow them to attack the motorcade,
如果我不让他们袭击车队
they're going to release canisters of nerve gas in multiple locations.
他们就会在人多的地方 释放神经毒气
You need to get out of the car!
你得赶快下车!
We're under attack; we need backup now!
我们遭到袭击 请求增援!
I thought we had an understanding.
我以为我们已经说好了的
It happened outside of my authority. I told no one.
这不在我职权范围之内 我没跟任何人说
If Russia isn't going to pay with the life of its president,
如何俄罗斯不能付出他们总统生命的代价
then its new ally, the United States,
那么他们的新盟友 美国
will pay with the lives of its citizens.
就要付出美国平民生命的代价
Mr. President, this is our final conversation. Good-bye.
总统先生 这是我们最后的通话 再见
No... Wait!
不... 等等!
The following takes place between 5Pm and 6Pm
以下是发生于傍晚5点至6点之间的故事
- How long has he been conscious? - Ten minutes.
- 他醒了多久了?  - 10分钟
Before you go in, you should be aware of something.
你进去之前 我得跟你说说
Tony's been asking for his wife.
托尼一直在问他妻子的情况
He doesn't remember?
他不记得了?
He remembers the explosion, but that's all.
他只记得爆炸
We have to tell him Michelle is dead.
我们不得不告诉他米歇尔已经死了
No, absolutely not. He's undergone severe trauma.
绝对不行 他受了严重的外伤 这种打击
This kind of stress will raise his blood pressure
会让他血压升高的
and make the vascular damage worse.
从而导致动脉血管受损更加严重
Please, just hold off on telling him until his condition has stabilized.
暂时不要告诉他真相 直到他的病情稳定下来
Would you excuse us, please?
能让我们单独谈谈吗?
Tony. How are you feeling?
托尼 感觉怎样?
They told me they took Michelle to Cedars.
他们告诉我米歇尔被送到斯德医院去了
Yes, they couldn't treat her here.
是的 这儿不能医治她
Why? How badly was she hurt?
为什么 她伤得有多重?
Is she going to be okay?
她不会有事吧?
As far as I know, yes.
到目前为止 不会有事的
What the hell's going on here, Bill?
到底发生了什么事情 比尔?
They killed President Palmer, and they tried to kill Michelle and me.
他们杀了帕默总统 然后又想杀死我和米歇尔
David Palmer was the primary target.
大卫・帕默是主要目标
They killed him because he was going to expose someone
他们杀他是因为帕默要揭露 洛根政府
inside Logan's administration. They set Jack up to take the fall.
里面的一个内奸 然后陷害到杰克头上
- Did they get Jack? - No. He's alive.
- 他们也杀了杰克?  - 不 他还活着
He's working with us here on a provisional basis.
他临时和我们一起工作
Bill, I need to talk to Jack.
比尔 我要和杰克谈谈
- You need to rest. - No, I don't need to rest.
- 你需要休息  - 不 我不需要休息
I need to talk to Jack. Now.
我要马上和杰克谈谈 马上
- I'll tell him. - Thanks.
- 我会告诉他的  - 多谢
Could you do me a favor?
可以帮我个忙吗?
Could you get a message to Michelle? Tell her I'm okay.
带个口信给米歇尔 告诉她我没事
I will.
我会的
Tony...
托尼...
We need you to get better.
我们需要你早日康复
Copy, Blacktop One. We're standing by.
收到 黑鹰一号 我们原地待命
The Navy helicopter is on its way, ma'am.
海军直升机马上就到了 夫人
It'll take us back to the retreat.
它会把我们带回去
He... didn't warn the motorcade.
他 他没有警告车队
Ma'am?
夫人?
Charles, he knew about the attack, and...
查尔斯 他知道有袭击 但是...
he just let it happen, Aaron.
他并没有阻止 艾伦
That can't be true.
这不可能
He didn't just let it happen. He...
他不仅没有阻止 还...
He gave the terrorists the Suvarovs' motorcade route.
还给了恐怖分子苏沃洛夫总统的行车路线
Ma'am, why would he do that?
夫人 他为什么要这样做?
How soon before you're ready?
还有多久可以准备好?
I'll be leaving in a couple of minutes.
几分钟我就会离开
I just need to finish setting the arming mechanism.
只剩下设置激活器
Make sure you place the canister to maximize casualties.
一定要把毒气罐的杀伤力放到最大
It must look as if this is one of our primary targets.
让它看起来就像是我们的主要目标
It'll be taken care of.
会搞定的
Yes?
讲
Do you have the key card yet?
拿到钥匙卡没有?
I'll have it within the hour.
一小时以内就能拿到
They're can be no miscues.
不能有任何失误
I'm using up one of my canisters to create this diversion.
我会用掉一个毒气罐转移他们的视线
Without the key card, it's all for nothing.
拿不到钥匙卡 一切都将是徒劳
Call me when you have it.
拿到后打给我
I will.
好的
-Hello. - I'm going to be there soon.
- 喂  - 我马上就到
Make sure you bring the money.
记得把钱带上
You'll have it.
钱会给你的
And you'll have your precious card.
那你也会拿到那张宝贵的卡
Careful. It's all we got left.
小心点 我们就剩这些了
Don't worry about it.
别担心
In a little while, be able to buy all you want.
过一会  我们能买你想要的东西
Mrs. Logan and the Suvarovs have been treated.
苏沃洛夫夫妇和洛根夫人已经没事了
The chopper is picking them up now.
直升机正把他们送过来
What do I say to my wife, Mike?
我该怎么和我妻子说 麦克?
She put you in an impossible situation...
她让你处于窘境...
It's my job to handle impossible situations,
我的工作就是处理这些不可能的情形
and I failed, and not for the first time.
可是失败了 不止一次
- Mr. President... - I should never have given in.
- 总统先生...  - 我不该妥协的
I should have ordered back the motorcade.
我本该叫回车队的
Sir, with all due respect, you don't have time for self-recrimination.
阁下 恕我冒昧  你现在没有时间自责了
The terrorists' attack failed.
恐怖分子袭击失败
We have to assume they'll make good on their threat
我们不得不认为 他们会兑现他们的承诺
to use the Sentox on American soil.
在美国本土使用Sentox毒气
Has CTU made any progress,
CTU有什么进展吗
or are they just waiting for the other shoe to drop?
还是在等更坏的事发生?
They're looking for a lead,
他们在找线索
working the scene where the motorcade was ambushed.
在车队被袭击的现场调查
Bill, they're airlifting the bodies of the terrorists to CTU.
比尔 他们正把恐怖分子 的尸体空运回CTU
When will they be here?
什么时候可以到?
Any minute. I'm meeting them in the morgue.
马上了 我去停尸房等着
- Let me know what you find. - You got it.
- 有发现就告诉我  - 明白
- Jack's calling in. - Put him on speaker.
- 杰克打电话来了  - 接到扬声器上
Jack, we're in an emergency briefing with department heads.
杰克 我们马上要向部门领导做紧急汇报
Bill wants to put you on speaker.
比尔要把你的电话接到扬声器上
I thought Lynn took Bill off the active roster.
我以为林已经把比尔解职了呢
Bill's been reinstated, and Lynn's been relieved of duty.
比尔复职了 现在林被解职了
- Okay, fine. Put me on. - All right. You're on.
- 好 接过去  - 好的 接通了
Jack, it's Bill. What did you find at Omicron?
杰克 我是比尔 你在欧米克隆发现了什么?
Christopher Henderson was responsible for setting up the deal
克里斯托夫・亨德森肯定参与了
that allowed the terrorists to gain control of the Sentox.
让恐怖分子得到Sentox毒气的 秘密交易
He just tried to kill me by blowing up a bunker
他炸了项目开发的地下掩体
that the Sentox was developed in.
他想干掉我
I managed to survive, but unfortunately the servers that control
我想办法活了下来 但不幸的是
the data were destroyed and Henderson managed to escape.
数据和服务器全被毁了 亨德森也跑了
- Chloe, are you there? - Go ahead, Jack.
- 科洛依 你在吗?  - 在 杰克
Can you hack into Henderson's office computer?
你能黑进亨德森办公室的电脑吗?
I already did it. Henderson's home workstation is clean.
我看过了 亨德森的电脑上什么都没有
He wiped his hard drive five minutes ago.
他五分钟前删除了硬盘上的所有数据
- There's still an active socket. - What's that mean?
- 但是还有一个活动的通讯接口  - 什么意思?
It means he's exchanging data with an off-site link.
就是说他通过远程连接传送了一些数据
Can you locate it?
你能找到地址吗?
Yeah. The registry listing is 5714 Tarawood Drive, Toluca Lake.
可以 注册地址是 塔拉伍德地区5714号 托卢卡湖
Tarawood Drive? That's his home address.
塔拉伍德地区? 是他家
I'll send a tac team.
我派一个战术分队过去
- No, Bill. I need to go in alone. - Why?
- 不 比尔 我一个人去?  - 为什么?
Henderson's good; he'll be able to detect a tac team moving in.
亨德森有两下子 派战术分队的话会被察觉的
How do you want to play this, Jack?
那你打算怎么办 杰克?
He left me for dead. I'm the last person he expects to see.
他以为我死了 他绝不会想到还能见到我
I should be able to walk up to his front door.
我应该可以直接从大门进去
All right. But I want you in constant contact with CTU.
好的 但是你得和CTU保持联系
Right now, Henderson is our primary link to finding this nerve gas.
现在 亨德森是我们寻找神经毒气的主要线索了
I know. I'll get back to you.
明白 我会和你联络的
You've reached the private client line for Banco Buenos Aires.
您已经接入布宜诺斯爱利斯公司的 私人客户专线
Please leave a message at the tone or
请在提示音后留言
press the star button for immediate assistance.
需要帮助 请按星号键
Client identification code, please.
请告知客户识别码
Eight-four-seven-seven-C, as in "Charlie."
8-4-7-7-C Charlie
How can I help you, Mr. Henderson?
有什么能为您效劳的吗? 亨德森先生
I'd like after-hours access to my personal safety deposit box, please.
我马上来拿我的私人安全保险箱
Yes, sir.
就办
Buchanan.
我是布坎南
Bill, we found a schematic of some kind of ventilation system
比尔 我们发现一个 好像是通风系统的结构图
on one of the terrorists. It's from the Suvarov attack.
在一个参与对苏沃洛夫袭击的恐怖分子的身上
Since that's the most efficient way to deliver the Sentox,
这是释放Sentox毒气最有效的办法
this could potentially be their next target.
所以极有可能是下一个目标
Do we know what building the schematic is from?
你知道是什么建筑的结构图吗?
Not yet. But I sent a copy off to Building and Safety.
还不知道 我已经给建筑安全部发过去了
They're running it against their archive.
他们正根据档案查询
Upload it to Chloe and Edgar. I want them working on this, too.
传给科洛依和埃德加 我要他们马上处理
Better make it fast.
最好快点
There's a number handwritten in the margin-- 18:00 hours.
边缘处有个手写的数字 6点
That means the attack could happen in the next hour.
这意味着袭击大概在一个小时内发生
Yeah.
是的
That was Curtis.
刚才是柯蒂斯
He's going to upload a set of schematics to our server.
他会上传一份结构图到我们的服务器上
This is the likely target of their next attack.
这很可能是下一个袭击目标
There was a time-stamp on it.
上面有时间标志
The attack could occur sometime in the next hour.
在一个小时之内袭击随时可能发生
- Where is it? - We don't know.
- 会在哪?  - 还不知道
The only thing Curtis could tell at first glance
柯蒂斯随便看了一下只能判断
is that it's the ventilation system in some kind of industrial building.
这是一个通风系统 好像在某种工业建筑里
How big?
有多大?
Big enough to hold several thousand people. Let's find it.
可以容纳几千人 赶快找吧
- How you doing, Tony? - Fine.
- 感觉如何 托尼?  - 还行
Have you heard anything else on my wife's condition?
你知道我妻子的情况吗?
I haven't heard anything new. Sorry.
我没听到什么新的消息 不好意思
Tony.
托尼
You'll have to get back to Recovery.
你必须回去休息
Get away from me.
走开
- Mr. Almeida, please... - I said get away from me!
- 阿尔梅达先生 请...  - 我说走开!
Tony, come on.
托尼 别这样
Michelle...
米歇尔...
- Thank God that you're all right. - Let go of me, or I'll...
- 谢天谢地你没事  - 放开我 不然...
- Martha, please... - Listen, don't touch me.
- 玛莎 别这样…  - 听着 别碰我
Martha, I'm sorry. I made a mistake.
玛莎 对不起 是我的错
I didn't think that I had any choice.
我真的没有选择余地
Charles... It isn't just that you...
查尔斯... 你不该...
You didn't stand up to them.
你不应该向他们妥协的
You should have stood up to them.
你本该勇敢的和他们斗争的
Martha...
玛莎...
Yuri, Anya,
尤里 恩雅
I can't tell you how glad I am that you're both all right.
非常高兴 看到你们平安无事
Thank you. It was awful.
谢谢 太可怕了
I'm deeply embarrassed that something like this could happen on U.S. soil,
我非常抱歉 这样的事情 竟然发生在美国境内
but I promise you, whoever did this will be brought to justice.
我向你保证 不管是谁干的 一定会受到法律的制裁
- Excuse me, Mr. President. - Of course.
- 失陪了 总统先生  - 请便
We both know who is responsible for this.
我们都知道是谁应该对此事负责
We believe it was the same group who attacked Ontario Airport this morning,
我们认为是今天早上袭击安大略机场 的恐怖分子干的
but we thought that they were all killed in the siege.
本来我们以为他们全部都被干掉了
Obviously, you were wrong.
显然你错了
The situation is much more serious than you know.
情况比你想像的还要复杂的多
These terrorists have possession of a military-grade nerve agent.
这些恐怖分子已拥有了 军用级别的神经毒气
And they've threatened to use it against the civilian population of Los Angeles.
他们威胁用来 对付洛杉矶的平民
- How long have you known this? - We just found out about it.
- 什么时候知道的?  - 就刚刚知道的
But given this change of circumstances,
由于目前恶劣的环境
I'm asking you to honor the terms of our treaty.
我请求您根据我们的签署的协议
Allow my intelligence and law enforcement agencies access
允许我们情报机构和执法部门
to whatever intelligence your security people have on these separatists.
获得你们的安全部门关于那些分裂份子的情报
- You will have our help. - Thank you, sir.
- 我们会帮忙的  - 谢谢 先生
Mr. President, I hope you won't find this offensive,
总统先生 希望你不要介意
but there's something that's been troubling me.
有件事情我很疑惑
- What is it? - Mrs. Logan-- her behavior.
- 是什么?  - 洛根夫人 她的行为
She has not been herself.
有点不正常
I'm sure that she is very upset by what just happened.
我肯定她是因为刚才的遭遇而感到不安
Yes, I imagine she would be, but I noticed this before the attack.
是的 可能是这样 但是我注意到 在袭击之前
From the time she entered the car with Anya and me.
从她进入车里和恩雅还有我在一起时 就这样了
Yuri, the truth is, my wife has been under a doctor's
尤里 是这样的 我妻子一直在接受医生的治疗
care for quite a while now.
已经有相当一段时间了
She suffers from depression and anxiety.
她患有 抑郁和焦虑症
It's been very difficult for both of us.
这对我们来说很艰难
- I'm sorry to hear that. - Thank you.
- 我很抱歉  - 谢谢
Guard said you wanted to see me?
警卫说你要见我?
How long are you going to keep me here?
你们要把我在这关多久?
You're not going out there any time today, Lynn.
今天你是出不去了 林
District Marshal's reviewing your case.
地区长官正在审理你的案子
I need to ask you a favor, Bill. I know I don't deserve it.
我希望你能帮我一个忙 比尔 我知道我不配
I was unfair to you earlier.
之前我对你不公
What is it?
帮什么?
I need to make a phone call.
我想打个电话
Lynn, if you think you can get out of this with a few phone calls,
林 你要以为你打几个电话
you're mistaken. I won't let that happen.
就能出去 那么你错了
It's not that, I swear it.
不是这事 我发誓
I'll give you the number, you can clear it yourself.
我可以给你号码 你可以检查
- What's this about? - My sister.
- 想打给谁?  - 我妹妹
I need to talk to her about a personal matter.
我和她之间有点私事
It can't wait a few hours?
就不能多等几小时?
No, it can't. Bill, please, she's in a little bit of trouble
不能等了 比尔 麻烦你下 她现在有点麻烦
and I'm the only one who can help her.
我是唯一能帮她的人
I don't need to clear it.
我不需要检查
Get Mr. McGill a phone. Give him some privacy.
给麦克基尔先生一个电话 让他单独待一会
Thank you.
谢谢
- Hello. - Jenny, it's me.
- 谁  - 詹妮 是我
Listen, I don't care that you took my wallet.
听着 我不在乎你拿走我的钱包
Keep everything that's in there.
里面的东西你随便拿
I just need to get my key card back.
我只想要回我的钥匙卡
- What key card? - My CTU access card.
- 什么钥匙卡?  - 我的CTU出入卡
It's of no value to you. It just lets me in and out of this building.
对你一点用都没有 是让我进出大门的
Well, can't you just get them to give you a new one?
那你要他们再给你一个新的不行吗?
I mean, that's what I did when I lost the key to my laundry room.
如果我丢了洗衣房的钥匙 我就这样办
Damn it, Jenny, this isn't a laundry room.
该死的 詹妮 这不是洗衣房
This is a secure government building.
这是安保严密的政府大楼
Now, if you don't want me to call the police,
如果你不想我报警的话
you'll get me back the key card today.
今天你必须把卡给我
- You hear me? - Yeah, I do.
- 听见了没?  - 好 我知道了
Listen, I got to go.
我要挂了
Where's that card from Lynn's wallet?
里恩钱包里的卡在哪?
Why?
怎么?
Cause I want to give him back his key card. We don't need it.
把他的钥匙卡还给他 我们留着没用
That's how I'm getting us all this money.
这可是咱们的摇钱树
You told me we were just going to take his cash and a credit card.
你不是说只拿现金和信用卡的
Yeah, we're taking a credit card.
是的 我们只拿信用卡
$20,000 line of credit, right here.
2万美元的信用卡 这就是
$20,000?
2万美元?
Who's going to pay you that kind of money?
谁会给你这么多钱买这东西?
Yes, Mr. President?
有事吗 总统先生?
I'd like to speak with my wife.
我想和我妻子谈谈
I'm sorry, sir. She asked to be left alone.
对不起 先生 她想要一个人静一静
Evelyn, I want to see my wife now. Move away from the door.
伊夫林 我要马上见我妻子 让开
Sir, she ordered me not to let anyone in.
她命令我 不要让任何人进来
I'm not anyone, Evelyn.
我不是别人 伊夫林
I know, sir, but she specifically mentioned you.
我知道 先生 但是她特别强调你不能进来
I have to get to a meeting.
我要开个会
Would you please tell my wife that I would like to speak with her?
请你转告我太太 我想和她谈谈
Of course, Mr. President.
好的 总统先生
Thank you.
谢谢
I'd like you to find Aaron Pierce right now.
我要你马上去把艾伦・皮尔斯找来
I want to know how he's doing.
我想知道他怎么样了
Is there a message you want me to get to him?
有什么需要我转告他的吗?
If he's all right, tell him I'd like to see him.
如果他没事的话  告诉他我要见他
Chloe, come here.
科洛依 来下
I think I got a match.
我想我找到了
There's a discrepancy here.
只有一点点不同
That's because they're from two different layers.
种类上的区分而已
The one Curtis had was structural,
柯蒂斯找到的是结构层
but this is an electrical blueprint.
我这个是电气层图纸
You're right. Mr. Buchanan.
对的 布坎南先生
Edgar matched the schematics we got from Curtis.
埃德加找到了 和柯蒂斯拿来的图纸相对应的
- Where is it? - Tyler Memorial. Westwood.
- 在哪?  - 泰勒莫瑞尔 韦斯特伍德
A hospital.
一家医院
Tell Curtis to activate a tac team.
叫柯蒂斯召集战术分队
I'll call Tyler Memorial, tell them to evacuate.
我打电话叫医院疏散
Operations.
接线员
Put me through to Tyler Memorial Hospital.
接泰勒莫瑞尔医院
This is Bauer. I'm on-site at the Henderson house.
我是鲍尔 我到亨德森家外面了
Do you copy?
你听到了吗?
Jack, we found intel in the body of a dead terrorist.
杰克 我们在一个恐怖分子 的尸体上发现了情报
There is going to be an attack.
他们打算马上发到袭击
- Where? - Tyler Memorial Hospital.
- 哪?  - 泰勒莫瑞尔医院
We think it's happening within the hour.
我们认为会在一小时内发生
Okay, I copy. I'm moving in now.
好的 收到 我现在进去了
- Miriam... - Who?
- 玛瑞安...  - 谁?
Christopher's wife. He's not here.
克里斯托夫的妻子 他不在
Tell Chloe I'll get back to her as soon as I have access to his computer.
告诉科洛依一旦我进入他的电脑 后就和她联系
All right, we're on it.
好的 我们准备好
This is Curtis Manning with CTU.
我是CTU的柯蒂斯・曼宁
I need to speak to the ranking security officer on site.
我要和现场的最高安全长官通话
You're talking to him. Tom Wegman.
我就是 汤姆・维格曼
Mr. Wegman, I'm heading to you now with a tactical team.
维格曼先生 我和战术分队正赶过来
The nerve gas will most likely be released into a ventilation unit.
神经毒气很可能释放在通风系统里
You need to seal off the sub-basement.
你要封锁地下2层
I've called in a second security shift.
我已经叫来了第二批轮班的安全人员
We'll get that area locked down.
好的 我们会把这里封锁
Good. How long before the hospital's evacuated?
医院疏散还要多久?
Uh, an hour, maybe two.
一小时 可能两小时
This attack could occur within the next 30 minutes.
30分钟后袭击可能就发生
This is a large facility, Agent Manning.
这是个大医院 曼宁特工
We have 600 patients, many of whom need assistance.
我们有600位病人  大部分都需要医疗护理
Mr. Wegman, if this nerve gas is released into the ventilation system,
维格曼先生如果神经毒气 被释放在通风系统
everyone inside that building will die.
医院里所有人都会死的
Do what you have to do,
尽最大的努力
but get those people out of that building.
把所有人都疏散出去
Right.
好的
Hello, Miriam.
你好 玛瑞安
Oh, my God. We thought you were dead.
天 我们以为你死了
Where is he?
他在哪?
What are you doing, Jack?
你要干什么 杰克?
Miriam, where's Christopher?
玛瑞安 克里斯托夫在哪?
He's still at work.
在上班啊
Did he call you?
他打电话给你过吗?
You're scaring me.
你吓着我了
In the last hour, has he called you?!
最近一小时 他有没有打电话给你?!
No. Now tell me what the hell is going on.
没 现在告诉我到底是怎么了
I need to see his computer.
我要看看他的电脑
- What are you doing? - Where is his computer?!
- 你要干什么?  - 他的电脑在哪?!
I'm not going to tell you anything until you tell me what is going on.
我不会告诉你 除非你告诉我到底是怎么了
Christopher developed a chemical weapons system
克里斯托夫在欧米克隆公司
called Sentox-VX nerve gas for Omicron.
研制了一种 叫Sentox-VX神经毒气的化学武器
He enabled terrorists to gain control of it,
他帮助恐怖分子得到了这种武器
now it's being used against civilian targets in Los Angeles.
现在正用于对付 洛杉矶的平民
So where is his computer?! Miriam, I am telling you the truth.
他电脑在哪 玛瑞安 我已经告诉你了真相
We have proof that he brokered the deal.
我们有他参与交易的足够证据
That's impossible.
那不可能
Less than an hour ago he tried to kill me.
不到一小时之前他还想杀了我
Move towards the living room.
到起居室去
Keep walking towards the den.
朝书房走
I want you to take a seat on the couch.
我要你坐在沙发上
Look, why don't we just call him? I'm sure there's an explanation.
要不 我们打电话给他? 肯定是有些误会
Miriam, take a seat.
玛瑞安 坐下
You don't need the gun, Jack.
你不用拿枪指着我 杰克
You're not going to shoot me.
你不会开枪的
Chloe, it's Jack.
科洛依 我是杰克
I need access to Henderson's hard drive.
我需要访问亨德森的硬盘
I need you to talk me through it.
我要你帮忙进入
Okay, Jack.
好的 杰克
Yes?
谁?
You wanted to see me, ma'am?
你找我 夫人?
Oh, yes, Aaron, come in.
是的 艾伦 请进
I didn't really get a chance to say thank you before.
我之前一直没有机会向你道谢
You saved my life.
你救了我
I know that you'll say it was all just in the line of duty.
我知道你想说 这是应该的
You're welcome.
不必客气
The country's lucky to have men like you.
国家很荣幸有你这样的人
I'm lucky.
我也很荣幸
I hope you'll allow me to say that.
希望你允许我这么说
Mrs. Logan.
洛根夫人
Would you excuse us, Aaron?
你能回避一下吗 艾伦?
What is it, Mike?
怎么了 麦克?
The President's been trying to reach you.
总统一直想找你
I know.
我知道
But I don't want to see him.
可我不想见他
Would you like me to convey that to the President?
我希望我把这意思 转达给总统吗?
You can convey whatever you want, Mike.
你想说什么都可以
Mike...
麦克...
Mike, I want you to know nothing happened in there.
麦克 我要你知道其实没发生什么
Whatever didn't happen, make sure it doesn't happen again.
不管有没有发生 你要保证以后不能再发生
- Manning? - Yeah.
- 曼宁?  - 是的
Tom Wegman, hospital security.
汤姆・维格曼 医院安全长官
Thanks for mobilizing your people so quickly.
谢谢你快速动员了你的手下
Have you uplinked with CTU yet?
你们和CTU联系了吗?
We're doing that now.
正在进行
We've doubled security at all sub-basement ingress points.
我们已经在所有的地下室入口加派了人手
Nobody's getting down there unless they go through us.
除非通过我们 否则没人能进去
Good.
非常好
The bad news is we have 26 patients in ICU that can't be moved.
糟糕的是加护病房还有26个病人 不能转移
Seven of them are high-dependency newborns.
7个是需要高度护理的新生儿
We can't even relocate them without the
没有特殊的转移设施
specialized transport units which we don't have on site.
我们不能安置他们 很不巧我们没有
What about nearby hospitals?
附近的医院呢?
All neonatal transport units are in service.
所有的这种装置都在使用当中
All right, thanks.
好的 谢谢了
I want a visual sweep of all high-probability target points within the hospital.
我要监控医院所有的可能攻击点
Team A, start at the north end,
A队 从北边开始
Team B take south. Move.
B队南边 行动
It's Viktor. I'm at the hospital.
我是维克多 我在医院
And why are you calling me?
为什么打电话给我?
They must have found out about the attack.
他们一定是发现了
The hospital's being evacuated.
医院正在疏散
All of the elevators and stairwells are guarded.
所有的电梯 和楼梯都有人看守
Calm down, Viktor. Bring up the schematics of the hospital.
冷静点 维克多 打开医院的结构图
There's another entrance to the sub-basement.
地下室还有另外一个入口
An electrical conduit.
一个电气管道
There's a good chance it isn't guarded.
很可能没人看守
How do I find it?
我怎么找?
In the Radiology wing down corridor six.
放射室下面的第6走廊
Call us when you're there. We'll talk you through it.
到了后给我们电话 我会指引你过去
I'll call you in a few minutes.
几分钟后打过去
Viktor, I need you to finish this task,
维克多 我要你必须完成这个任务
even if it means you don't get out.
即使你不能活着出来
I won't fail you.
不会让你失望的
DOD just concluded a briefing with Russian Intelligence.
国防部和俄罗斯情报部门 刚联系了一下
We were given a name. Vladimir Bierko.
我们得到个名字 弗拉德米尔・比耶科
He made billions in the post-Soviet economy-- weapons and oil.
他通过前苏联的 武器和石油交易赚了几十亿
He bankrolled several underground radical publications promoting the separatist cause,
他赞助了几个宣传分裂主义的地下激进刊物
but it's believed that he was more than just a sympathizer.
但是他应该不仅仅是赞助者
The Russians think he's financing these attacks?
俄罗斯还认为他为袭击提供经费?
They think that he's directing the attacks himself.
甚至认为他直接指挥这些袭击
Based on what?
根据什么?
A number of communiques that were intercepted by the Russian security force,
俄罗斯安全部门 截获的一些信息
supported by the fact that Bierko vanished from Russia 3 months ago.
还有比耶科已经 从俄罗斯消失了3个月
We posted Bierko's profile to the interagency servers.
我们把比耶科的资料 放到了内部服务器上
Homeland Security has issued an emergency brief to local law enforcement.
国土安全部也给地方部门发布了紧急通知
Do you think there's any hope of finding him
你认为有希望在 泰勒医院被袭击之前
before the attack on Tyler Hospital?
找到他吗?
The most promising lead we have is a man named Christopher Henderson.
最有价值的线索 是一个叫克里斯托夫・亨德森的人
Unfortunately, he escaped.
不幸的是 他跑了
Jack Bauer believes there may be files on Henderson's computer
杰克・鲍尔认为亨德森的电脑上
that could lead us to Bierko.
可能有信息能帮我们找到比耶科
He's trying to acquire those files now, sir.
他正在试图获取这些文件 先生
Well, let's hope he succeeds, Bill.
好吧 希望他成功 比尔
The country's already suffered three devastating attacks today.
国家今天已经遭受了 三次毁灭性的打击了
- We need to stop this madman. - Yes, Mr. President.
- 我们必须得阻止这个疯子  - 会的 总统先生
Chloe, it's Jack. Have you found anything yet?
科洛依 我是杰克 找到什么了吗?
The only thing on Henderson's hard drive is domestic stuff:
亨德森的硬盘上 只有一些常见的文件
bill-paying programs, downloaded music.
付账程序 下载的音乐
Chloe, Henderson isn't trading music files with his office.
科洛依 亨德森不会和办公室传送音乐文件
There's something else on the computer. Find it.
电脑上一定还有些什么 找出来
I'm doing the best I can.
我在努力
Why don't you face it, Jack? Christopher is innocent.
你为什么就不能接受呢 杰克? 克里斯托夫是无辜的
He was innocent when you forced him out of CTU, and he's innocent now.
你把他赶出CTU的时候就是无辜的 现在仍然是
Maybe you didn't hear me earlier, Miriam, he tried to kill me.
玛瑞安 可能你之前没听清我的话 他想杀我
If he did, then he was defending himself.
他这样做 一定是想自卫
No, he blew up the server room at Omicron while I was still inside.
不 他炸了欧米克隆公司的服务器室 当时我还在里面
He was destroying evidence that would have implicated him in this conspiracy.
他在销毁可暴露他同谋的证据
This is so familiar. You're accusing him of being a criminal.
你们又这样 又要指控他犯罪
Why do you hate him so much?
你为什么这么恨他?
I want you to know something.
我希望你知道
Chris never hated you, not even after what you did to him.
克里斯从来不恨你 即使你那样对他
When he thought you were dead, he looked in on Kim.
当他以为你死了之后 他探望过金
He cared about your daughter, Jack, just like he cared about you.
他很关心你女儿 杰克 就象他很关心你一样
We both did. You know that.
我们都很关心你 你知道的
- I found something, Jack. - What is it?
- 我找到些东西了 杰克  - 是什么?
It's a shadow drive. It was partitioned from the primary hard drive.
一个隐藏分区 从主盘上分出来的
What's on the shadow drive?
隐藏分区上面有什么?
A backup log that contains data points for every satellite phone call
一个备份文件 记录了亨德森去年打的
Henderson has made in the last year.
所有卫星电话
Can you cross-reference those numbers
你可以把那些号码
with the telephone numbers the terrorists used earlier this morning?
和今天早上恐怖分子用过的 对照一下吗?
I got into the log, but the phone lists are password-protected.
我进入了记录文件 但是电话清单有密码保护
Hold on.
等等
Christopher had a secret file on his computer. There's a list of numbers.
克里斯托夫电脑上有个秘密文件 里面有很多数字
And that implicates him?
这能说明他什么?
We need access to that list.
我们需要打开这个列表
- Do you know the password? - No, I don't.
- 你知道密码吗?  - 不 我不知道
Miriam, we believe there's going to be another attack within 30 minutes.
玛瑞安 我们相信半小时之内 另一次袭击就会发生
Thousands of lives are at stake.
数以千计的人危在旦夕
Please, if you know that password, I need it now.
考虑下 如果你知道密码 请告诉我
I can't help you.
我帮不了你
Chloe, you're going to have to try and hack into it.
科洛依 需要你来破解密码了
I'll see what I can do.
我试试看
Hurry.
抓紧
I'll show this to Manning.
我会给曼宁看
Agent Manning?
曼宁探员?
One of our guards caught this.
我们的一个警卫发现的
This guy's dressed as an orderly, but I've never seen him before.
这个人打扮像个勤务工 但是我们以前没见过
An orderly has no business being where he is.
勤务工不可能在这里出现
That was five minutes ago.
这是五分钟前的
- Where is this? - Sub-basement.
- 这是哪?  - 地下室
Team A, meet me in the southeast stairwell.
A队 在东南的楼梯会合
Team B, form a soft perimeter.
B队 设置警戒
We have a possible suspect in play.
发现了嫌疑犯
- CTU, did you copy that? - Yes, we copy.
- CTU 收到没有?  - 收到
Edgar, I need you to uplink the hospital video surveillance
埃德加 我需要你 连接医院的监控系统
for facial recognition software. See if you can get a match.
运行面部识别软件 看能否找到匹配的
Got it.
就办
Curtis has a suspect.
柯蒂斯发现一个嫌疑犯
We're running the image through facial recognition.
我们正在使用面部识别系统
Halfway through the database.
数据库已经查找过半了
- Got something. - All right, put it up.
- 找到了  - 好的 调出来
Curtis, we have a suspect.
柯蒂斯 找到了这个嫌疑犯
His name is Viktor Grigorin. He's a Russian national.
他的名字叫维克多・格里高利 俄罗斯人
Served time for drug smuggling and weapons trafficking.
因走私毒品和武器被判过刑
Copy that.
收到
All teams, suspect is a confirmed hostile.
全体队员 疑犯已经确认
Repeat: a confirmed hostile.
疑犯已经确认
Freeze!
不许动!
Agent Manning, you need to come look at this.
曼宁探员 过来看看这个
Search him.
搜他的身
Don't! It might be set to go off if it's moved.
别 移动可能会释放
Chemical Response Team, we need you down here now.
化学反应小组 我这需要你们马上过来
All teams, we've located the canister, and it is armed.
全员注意 我们发现了毒气罐 已经被启动
Repeat: the canister is armed.
重复 毒气罐已启动
CTU, Chemical Response Team is on the way in.
CTU 化学小组正在进来
The hospital evacuation is still in progress.
医院的疏散还在进行当中
There are still a lot of people in here.
这里还是有很多人
Copy that, Curtis.
收到 柯蒂斯
Edgar, notify LAPD and all relevant agencies.
埃德加 通知洛杉矶警察局和所有相关机构
I want a mandatory evacuation of the downtown core.
市中心要实施强制疏散
Yes, sir.
是 先生
Jack, Henderson is using an interlaced encryption key.
杰克 亨德森使用的是 一种特殊加密法
What does that mean?
什么意思?
It could take me a half a day to crack it.
我要花半天才能解开
Damn it, Chloe, we don't have that kind of time.
科洛依 我们没有这么多时间
I'm sorry. It's a little tougher than it looked at first glance, okay?
抱歉 看来估计就得这样
Yeah. All right.
好吧
Jack, you should know that Curtis and his team
杰克 柯蒂斯和他的人
intercepted a terrorist at the hospital.
在医院抓到一个恐怖分子
- Did they take him into custody? - No. He's dead.
- 关押起来了吗?  - 没 他死了
But they found a nerve gas canister. They're trying to disarm it now.
但他们发现一只毒气罐 他们正在设法拆除
There are patients there that can't be evacuated.
医院还有很多人无法撤离
Chloe, listen to me. There's nothing you can do about the hospital.
科洛依 听我说 医院那里你无能为力了
There's still 18 canisters out there. I need you to stay focused.
外面还有18个毒气罐 我需要你集中精神
I know.
知道
If I got you more personnel, would that help you crack the code faster?
如果多给你人手 是不是能帮你破解的快一点?
I've already got three analysts working on it, Jack.
已经有三个分析员在弄了 杰克
Miriam?
玛瑞安?
Miriam? Honey, I want you to pack a bag. I want you...
玛瑞安? 亲爱的 马上收拾行李 我要你...
Don't you move!
别动!
Miriam, sit back down!
玛瑞安 坐回去!
Put your hands behind your head. Get back up on your knees.
把手放到头后 起来跪着
Now!
快!
I want you to handcuff yourself. Behind your back.
反手把自己铐上
Get up.
起来
Take a seat next to Miriam on the couch.
坐在玛瑞安旁边 到沙发上
- You okay, honey? - I'm okay.
- 你没事吧 亲爱的?  - 没事
How do I find the nerve gas?
告诉我怎么找到毒气?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
我不知道你在说什么
Where is it?
在哪?
That's right, Jack. Start at my knee, just like I taught you.
好吧 杰克 从我的膝盖开始  就象我以前教你的一样
Sooner you do it, sooner you'll see I don't know what you're talking about.
你下手越快 就会越早发现我其实什么都不知道
Where is it?!
在哪?!
He doesn't know, Jack! He doesn't know!
他不知道 杰克! 他不知道!
For God's sake, leave him alone!
看在老天的份上 放过他吧!
Christopher, CTU found one of the canisters at Tyler Memorial Hospital.
克里斯托夫 CTU在泰勒医院发现了一个毒气罐
It's armed! People are going to start dying.
已经被启动 会死很多人的
How do I find the nerve gas?
我怎么找到神经毒气?
Jack, leave him alone! He doesn't know anything!
杰克 放过他吧 他什么都不知道
You really trust him?
你真的相信他?
Ask him what's in the briefcase.
问他手提箱里是什么东西
Unlock it!
打开!
Ask him what he's doing with all the money!
问他是什么 问他这些钱是做什么用的!
- Ask him! - Christopher?
- 问他!  - 克里斯托夫?
Is this true? Have you been lying to me all this time?
是真的吗 你一直在对我撒谎?
I've been protecting you all this time.
我一直在保护你
- By lying? - It's not that simple, Miriam.
- 用欺骗的方式?  - 没有那么简单 玛瑞安
- I defended you. - I defended you, too,
- 我在保护你  - 我也在保护你
against things you would not want to know because I love you, Miriam.
因为我爱你 玛瑞安 有些事情不能告诉你
There's not one thing I've done out of self-interest or greed.
我做的这些事没有一件是为了私利
Even when they fired me-- even when they framed me--
即使当他们解雇我 当他们陷害我的时候
I served my country.
我也是对国家忠诚的
I don't care how you justify this. I am out of time.
我不管你怎么辩解 我没时间了
You are going to tell me now how to find the rest of the nerve gas.
你必须马上告诉我 如何找到剩余的神经毒气
Oh, go ahead and do it, Jack. Get it done. Shoot me.
来吧 动手 杰克 动手吧 开枪
Kneecap me. Go ahead and do it. Do it!
打我的膝盖 来吧 动手吧 快动手!
- You son of a bitch! - I shot her above the kneecap!
- 你个婊子养的!  - 我打的是大腿
- Son of a bitch! - She can still walk!
- 婊子养的!  - 她还可以走路!
You make me shoot her again,
如果你逼我再开枪的话
she'll be in a wheelchair for the rest of her life!
她的下半生就要在 轮椅上度过
Damn you!
他妈的!
Where do I find the nerve gas?!
哪里可以找到毒气?!
Where is it?
在哪?
Please, please, baby.
求你了 求你了  宝贝
Don't you make me do this.
别逼我这样做
Tell him what he wants to know.
告诉他他想知道的吧
I can't.
我不能
Forgive me, Miriam. I can't.
原谅我吧 玛瑞安 我不能这样
You son of a bitch.
你这个婊子养的
You don't care about anybody.
你谁也不在乎
Not even her.
即使是她
Chloe, this is Jack. I need an ambulance on site.
科洛依 我是杰克 我需要一辆救护车
I repeat: I need an ambulance on site.
重复一遍 我需要一辆救护车
Miriam Henderson's been shot in the leg.
玛瑞安腿部中枪
I'm bringing Christopher Henderson in to CTU.
马上带克里斯托夫・亨德森回CTU
I'll need an interrogation room prepped,
我需要准备好审问室
and a medic standing by with hyocine-pentothal.
还要一个药物审讯医生待命
It'll be ready when you get here.
你到之前准备就绪
- You okay, Jack? - Yeah, I'm fine.
- 你没事吧 杰克?  - 没事
- Just get the ambulance here now. - Team's on its way.
- 快叫救护车来  - 上路了
Put Buchanan on.
帮我接布坎南
Mr. Buchanan, Jack's on line one.
布坎南先生 杰克在一号线
Jack, it's Bill.
杰克 我是比尔
What's happening at the hospital?
医院那边情况怎么样?
There's a CRT team on site. Stand by, Jack.
现场有化学小组处理 等等 杰克
Curtis, what's your status?
柯蒂斯 你那里情况如何?
We're still trying to defuse the detonator.
我们还在试着拆除
Look what we found on the hostile.
这是我在敌人身上找到的
Hold on, Bill.
等等 比尔
It's a remote timing display.
是一个遥控定时器
- Can we defuse the detonator? - Not in 60 seconds.
- 你能马上拆除吗?  - 60秒内不可以
We'll have to get it out of here.
那我们就要把它带出去
It could go off if we move it.
移动的话有可能会释放的
It's a chance I'm gonna have to take.
我们必须要冒这个险
All teams, we're moving the canister to the containment unit.
全体队员注意 我们要移动毒气罐 到一个密封的装置
All right, go, go, go, go, go!
好了 走 走 走!
All right, clear the hall! Clear the hall!
走 走 走! 快点 快点!
We're coming through.
我们来了
Go, go, go!
让 让 让
Make sure the door is open.
清障 清障 清障
Upstairs! Upstairs!
上楼了 上楼了
Go, go, go! Clear the hall!
走开 走开 走开!
Get out of the way! Get out of the way!
快 快 快!
Keep the hall clear! Coming through!
清障 大家都让开
Get that door open.
把门打开!
Get it in there.
快 放进去
We're clear.
安全了!
CTU...
CTU...
the canister detonated inside a containment unit.
毒气在一个密封装置里释放了
The hospital's safe.
医院安全了
Good work, Curtis.
干的好 柯蒂斯
I have the key card.
我拿到钥匙卡了
How long will it take for you to reprogram it?
需要多久重写程序
Five minutes.
5分钟
Then we will be able to use it to access CTU.
然后CTU大门就敞开了
Good.
好样的